<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Docker on Kenwolverine</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/tags/docker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docker on Kenwolverine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blogs/tags/docker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Docker Tutorials&#43;Insights&#43;Exp</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/posts/docker_tie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/posts/docker_tie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;: I am not going to say the same things that are said in the documentations but i am going to share what i learnt and understood about it along with insights and experiences as the tittle suggests and things that are related to the environment is based on &lt;code&gt;fedora 41&lt;/code&gt; only because that&amp;rsquo;s what i use :&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;docker-&#34;&gt;Docker:-&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Based on my understanding docker is used to solve one of the most important classic problem of the entire software community which is &amp;ldquo;It works on my computer without any errors but why doesn&amp;rsquo;t it work in your&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo;. But if you ask me &amp;ldquo;does docker became famous for just solving that one particular problem&amp;rdquo;, I would say that it&amp;rsquo;s kind of a very big problem that was solved by docker which made it cool but it&amp;rsquo;s not the only problem it solves. Docker provides lot of other features which helps us seperate our code from the system thus enhancing security and efficiency and it also allows us to run multiple code at the same time but the cool part is each and every code runs on its own container without affecting each other. Let&amp;rsquo;s say you are fond of developing stuffs but you just have one system and you want ot run multiple projects but here&amp;rsquo;s the catch each project requires different versions of the same environment, now that&amp;rsquo;s a problem right ofcourse i know you can run in &lt;code&gt;virtual environments(VENV)&lt;/code&gt; if you are using &lt;code&gt;python&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;nvm&lt;/code&gt; for &lt;code&gt;Nodejs&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;jEnv&lt;/code&gt; for &lt;code&gt;java&lt;/code&gt; and so on.. but if you need strict isolation docker is your man, focussing on security and portability without affecting the performance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
